You might also be interested to know the Centre is running a pilot scheme of talks ofr patients.
你也许对这个感兴趣，中心正在运营一项与病人谈话的试验计划。
I've got the list here.Actually,they look very interesting.
我这里有一个单子，事实上，它们看起来很有趣。
What sort of things?
什么样的事情？
Well,the first one's about giving up smoking.
第一个是关于戒烟的。
It's next week,the twenty-fifth of February,at 7 pm,and that's in Room 4.
在下周，2月25日晚上7点，4号房间。
It says,the talk will stress the health benefits particularly for people with asthma or heart disease.
会谈主要讲的是针对哮喘和心脏病人的健康福利。
That sounds very interesting.
听起来很有趣。
There's also a talk for families with children.
还有关于有孩子的家庭的讲话。
It's on Healthy Eating, and takes place on the first of March at five o'clock.
它在3月1日的5点，“健康饮食”举行。
Will that be at the Health Centre?
这是在健康中心里吗？
Erm,actually it's at the primary school on Shore Lane.
事实上是在Shore Lane的一家小学里。
I imagine they're inviting the parents of pupils there - it says here 'all welcome'.
我想他们会邀请小学生的家长，这上面写的是“全部欢迎”。
Mmm,I might go to that if I have time.
如果我有时间，我会去。
There's a couple of other talks - one giving advice about how to avoid injuries while doing exercise.
这里有许多其他的谈话，一个是关于如何避免在运动中受伤。
It's on the ninth of March.
这是在3月9日。
Oh,it's a late afternoon talk,at four thirty,and it'll be in Room 6.
这是下午晚些时候的讲话，在4:30，6号房间。
It also says the talk is suitable for all ages.
上面还说这个讲话适合所有年龄层。
And finally,there's a talk called 'Stress Manaement' which is...
最后一个讲话是压力管理……